wisdomjobs.co.za 2015-03-19

# Privacy Policy | Wisdomjobs.co.za

#### Introduction

We, at ['Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.'](http://www.wisdomitservices.com/), are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for suitable protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. 

"Personal Information" contains any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. For further information, you can visit ['Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.'](http://www.wisdomitservices.com/) web pages with confidentially or without revealing any personal information about yourself. 

#### Technologies used for tracking

Some of our web pages utilize **"cookies"** and other tracking technologies. A **"cookie"** is denoted as a small text file used to collect information about web site activity. Some cookies and some other technologies may serve to remind personal information previously indicated by a web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

You may set most browsers to notify, if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. If a user’s system is idle for more than one hour, the cookies will expire and you need to enter your Email Id and Password to login into your account to continue the same session. It is a security measure to prevent from unauthorized access of the system when the user is not at system. 

Tracking technologies may record information such as internet domain and host names; internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; click stream patterns; and dates and times of the accessing details of the user. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our web site. We may also analyze the information that does not contain personal information for trends and statistical analysis. 

#### External Services

Third parties provide certain services available on ‘www.wisdomitservices.com’ on 'Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.' Behalf of 'Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.'.The provided information may contain personal information, that 'Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.' collects on the web to third-party service providers to help us deliver programs, products, information, and services. Service providers are also an important means by which 'Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.' maintains its web site and mailing lists. 'Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.' will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect personal information on Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.'s behalf. 

'Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.'does not intend to transfer personal information without your consent to third parties, who are not bound to act on Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.'s behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.'s policy to sell personal information collected online without your consent.

#### Your Commitment

By using this Web site, your consent to the terms of our online privacy policy and to Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.'s processing of personal information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where ‘Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd. collects personal information on the web. 

#### Security Measures   
  
---  
  
  * We ensure maximum security standards to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data of yours.
  * We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.

#### Updating your information

| TOP  
|   | 

  * We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information for many of our services. For more information, please see the help pages for each service.

---|---  
  
#### Restricting Information Sharing and Disclosure   
  
| 

We process the data/information which we’ve received to our site to can also be processed at outside of the country including SOUTH AFRICA. The process of information may change along with the countries as the data protection laws may differ from one country to other country. To access your information on our Site/Partner sites by employers/users may apply different laws as per their country legal procedures.

‘Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt.Ltd.’does not lease, sell, or share personal information about you with third party(save with your consent) or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:  
  
---  
  
  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with 'Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.' under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help 'Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.' communicate with you about offers from 'Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.' and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We consider that it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.'s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We have the right to transfer information about you incase 'Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.' is acquired or merged with another company. In this event, 'Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.' will intimate you before information is transferred to the new company and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

'Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.' Is also having the right to display the targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with you may view, or click on targeted ads  to meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.  
  
  * 'Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.' does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted advertisement. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the advertisement.
  * 'Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.' advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).

' **Wisdom IT Services (India) Private Ltd.'** works with business partners like vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers of various industries and business. For more information regarding services provides and other products please go through our detailed reference links.   

#### Confidentiality and Security   
  
  * We provides limited access to personal information about you to employees, who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * "We also have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that meet the terms with legal parameters in India to protect personal information about you. We seek to ensure compliance with the requirements of the Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules made there under to ensure the protection and preservation of your privacy policy.

| TOP  
  
We can ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information should be disclosed in a way as mentioned in this Privacy Policy. As a user of the Sites, you understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Sites, the internet generally, and the documents you post or access and for your conduct on and off the Sites.  
  
#### Tips to protect from Frauds  
  
Don’t provide the below details which were asked by third parties. The below important tips may be useful to protect from frauds:  
  
  * We never ask you to provide social security number to a prospective employer. 
  * We never ask you to provide your credit card or bank numbers or force to engage in a monetary transaction of any kind. 
  * Be alert when you are dealing with the parties rather than your country.
  * We never ask you to provide the details not related with professional aspects like social security number, eye color, marital status, etc. through telephone or online.

| TOP  
  
#### Some other tips for your privacy

|   
  
  * We never ask you to provide your personal information to do job search in wisdom IT services and its partner sites. So, never provide any personal information to perform job search in our site. You can also do your search without logging in to the site.
  * Your resume will be put in front of the thousands of employers once you have posted your resume with Wisdom IT services and its partner sites. We will create a separate Login Id and password with the details you have provided. 
  * You can use the Login Id and Password to do edit in your resume if you want.
  * 

|   
  
#### Edit your personal information

|    
  
  * You can correct the personally identified information provided with Wisdom IT Services and its partner sites. If you want to stop our services may also contact us by sending an Email or calling us to the Telephone numbers mentioned in **Contact Us** page.
  * Your accounts will be retained as long as you desire our services. Incase if you want to delete, deactivate or remove the changes in Membership information you may contact us at [jobseekers@wisdomjobs.co.za](mailto:jobseekers@Wisdomjobs.co.za) or [support@wisdomjobs.co.za](mailto:support@Wisdomjobs.co.za) or filling the details of **Contact Us** page.
  * We have an official blog, which is free accessible and the information provided in these areas may be accessed by all. You can send a request to us to remove your personal details from blog by sending an email or through **Contact Us** from. We’ll incorporate your request if it is able to do, otherwise we’ll let you know the reason why we are unable to do it.

|    
  
#### Contact Information

|    
‘Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt.Ltd.’welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement at the contact address given at the website. We invite your concerns about contravention of this Privacy Policy; ‘Wisdom IT Services (India) Pvt.Ltd.’will employ all commercially reasonable efforts to address the same. You can **Contact Us** always by sending your queries. |    
  |    
  
#### Updating this Privacy Policy

|    
The terms and policies proposed in this document may be changed at any time along with our policy changes. We’ll let you know through email, before the change become effective. Please go through our Page regularly to be aware about our privacy policies. Using our services may denote that, you are agreed to our policy specifications.  |
